when thinking about your future it's
normal to have some worries but that
shouldn't stop you from taking charge of
your retirement Journey today three
enforc singaporeans do not have a
retirement insurance plan however we
dream about retiring at a preferred age
of 57 with hopefully $ 1.1 million
Singapore dollars in retirement savings
no matter what retirement means to you
manual life Singapore can help you get
started with manual life smart retire 3
Manu life smart retire 3 offers a
specially curated list of funds you can
choose from to channel your Investments
to the wide range of funds is assessed
by manual Life Investment Management
through qualitative and quantitative
assessments and you have the freedom to
select a mix of funds based on your risk
appetite and investment objectives your
selected funds will work to accumulate
your retirement Nest a as you put in
your regular premiums and the longer you
stay invested the more resilient your
portfolio will be against Market
volatility
throughout the policy you can also
switch funds as you deem fit if you have
chosen dividend paying funds you can
even opt to reinvest or withdraw the
potential dividends on top of that
manual life smart retire 3 provides you
with additional bonuses to further boost
your investment such as welcome bonus
from the start and yearly loyalty
bonuses from your accumulation period
and onward as we work with you towards
your retirement goal manual life smart
retire 3's protection benefits can save
guard your retirement dreams from
unexpected events these include a death
benefit and a waiver of premium on
cancer during your minimum investment
period at the start of your accumulation
period your protection amount will bump
up to the total of your chosen Target
retirement amount protecting you against
death and total and permanent disability
during your retirement period the death
benefit will be equal to the amount of
your account value what's more this plan
boasts a unique feature that refunds the
cost of insurance back into your policy
if protection benefits are not utilized
if no claims are made during the minimum
investment period the cost of insurance
will be refunded into the policy during
the accumulation period similarly if no
claims are made during the accumulation
period the cost of insurance will be
refunded into the policy during the
retirement period for your retirement
needs plans and dreams manual life smart
retire 3 is here for you guaranteed
acceptance with no health questions
asked speak with your manual Life
Financial Consultant or visit any dbsp
USB Branch today
[Music]